https://www.prisonerseducation.org.uk/privacy-policy-cookies/

Login area
Search for:
Accessibility
We are committed to protecting your privacy.
How do we collect information?
We will collect and use personal information from you when you use electronic forms on our website to enquire about our activities, register with us, sign up to e-news or otherwise provide us with personal information.
If you are registering to be a user on the PET website, your information will be stored on our website server to support your online profile as you use our site. The server is GDPR compliant and all information is encrypted.
Information submitted through all other forms will be stored temporarily on the website server, but will be downloaded on a fortnightly basis to PET servers (hosted by our IT support company, Office Tech Hub), and removed from website servers.
What information do we collect?
The types of information collected will depend on which website form you are using. It might include your name, date of birth, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, place of work, mobile number and past experience of the criminal justice system.
IP data is also collected anonymously using a cookie on the website.
How do we use this information?
We will use your personal information to provide you with the information, products or services you have requested and you will be provided a copy of and/or given access to any additional relevant privacy notice as needed (for example our volunteer privacy notice if you have opted to become a PET volunteer). IP data informs Google Analytics which PET and our website support company (Ave Design) use to monitor user behaviour to improve the experience of those who visit our website.
Will we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
We will never disclose the information you give to us to outside parties unless circumstances mean that we are required to do so by law.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the use of your data on our website, please email the Chief Executive, Rod Clark, rod@prisonerseducation.org.uk.
If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are not processing your personal data in accordance with the law and have a complaint that you believe has not been adequately dealt with by our complaints procedure, you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office https://ico.org.uk/
About us
Our History
Get involved
Volunteer
What we do
Stories
Join our mailing list
Email
